[{"answer": "Well, let's start with the Tokyo Stock Exchange.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "Kyung, what is the latest over there?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "What the hell is going on?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "No, it isn't an American problem and it is everyone's problem.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "It's not just an American problem, is it?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Well, if he was hoping to reassure investors out there, Piers, he failed because when he started speaking just before 2:00 Eastern Time here in the United States, the Dow was down about 400 points.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "They really didn't get it, did they?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "It certainly is a national emergency right now.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "And shouldn't the senior politicians be reconvening to deal with this?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Yes, you're exactly -- you're exactly right.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Ali, what do you think?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "They do.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Don't they?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Wolf, yes or no?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Erin?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Ali?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "People in Asia think so.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "ORGAN: Kyung?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Well, the probability of a double dip recession right now, in my view, is at least 50 percent.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "And if we are facing this catastrophe, what can President Obama do about it to stop it from happening?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "They don't.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "And storms don't get much bigger than this, do they?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "I cannot speak to Mr. Soros.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Do you that if there are other people out there making a killing as everybody else loses?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I think a double dip reselling is at this point very likely.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Yes or no, do you think?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "High risk can be averted, but a high risk.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Mohamed El-Erian, yes or no, double dip recession?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Well, the first thing you have to do is not sell into a falling market.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "How should people take care of their money?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "And here's the worst news.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "But the bad news is the value of those 401(k)s has been sliding, right?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Is it happening again?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "My gut feeling tells me we're in for a little bit of a rough ride.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "What's your gut feeling?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "I actually had a conversation with my wife about this over the week.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "What would you like to hear from him?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Let's be clear, we're a long way from that.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Could you see that coming to America?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Quite frankly, economic weakness is a time of opportunity, if you're prepared for it.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "How bad is this from your point of view, from a guy that runs a big company in America?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Well, obviously it starts with confidence.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "How do you reenergize the jobs market?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "With a straight face then, right?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "The reason that the Asian markets and the South Pacific markets are lower is quite simply, having seen such a dramatic fall on Wall Street, there was no way they can stand as a bulwark against that tidal wave of selling and market turmoil.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "What is the global perspective?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "I think whatever it started out as on Saturday night, after the shooting earlier last week by the police of someone -- I think whatever it started out as has long since gone.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "I suppose the obvious question I want to put to you is how much of this is just opportunistic gangsterism, if you like, by disaffected youth, and how much of it is indicative of an underlying social problem caused by the financial malaise?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Piers, I have the shirt on my back and I have managed to keep it there for all these years because I've never given a prediction on where the market is going.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "How do you see things going?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Yes, I think in some places we are heading for it.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "You know, I mean, it is like the war on crime.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Is this an unwinnable war now?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Well, I think for the SEAL community, it's a very tight community.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "What affect will that have on the moral there for the American military?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "As you say, when you're seeing ten years on, the rangers and the SEALs really struggling, it should send a message, shouldn't it?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Are there any tangible things that we can identify that have been progress made, if you like?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Well, what started off as a bad day, Piers, is starting to look even worse.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Kyung, where are we right now?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Traders are certainly bracing for that, that this is just the beginning.", "docId": "110808pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Is it going to get worse and worse, do you think?", "qSentId": 576}]